santu.com 2009-10-18

# sell anything, anywhere, anytime with santu sell anywhere links

**At Santu, we take your privacy seriously and pledge to respect the confidentiality of any information you provide about yourself.**

### Securing your privacy

We do not rent, sell, share or give personal information about you to other people or companies; nor do we provide any information on orders you may accept via our servers.

We are however bound by international regulations which require us to release your personal data in the unlikely event of a legal process.

This Privacy Policy covers Santu's handling of the personal information collected from merchants, who use the GlobeCharge order processing and payment gateway services. It also covers the customer information that we obtain in the course of our business.

This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Santu does not control or own, or to people that Santu does not employ or supervise. Santu is a wholly owned subsidiary of GlobeCharge Pty. Ltd. This Policy is specific to Santu and does not apply to other services provided by GlobeCharge.

### Collection and use of information

Santu gathers personally identifiable information whenever you register for a Santu account, or use specific Santu products and services. This also applies to other business partners, and resellers.

When you register with Santu, we request your contact information (including your name, residential address and e-mail address), as well as specific information about your business, including bank account and/or credit card numbers. This infomration is also used to set up a GlobeCharge account on your behalf.

When processing a payment transaction, Santu generally receives transaction-related information from the merchant or financial institution. This usually includes information about the payment that a consumer has made to the merchant or financial institution. Santu does not acquire direct information about your customers from the santu checkout pages.

The information collected by Santu is used to carry out your requests for particular products and services; to facilitate billing; to process payment transactions; and to otherwise provide the payment gateway services. Merchants may also be sent announcements regarding; new Santu products and services, periodic specials, newsletters, service announcements, products and services offered by Santu's business partners.

Note: personally identifiable consumer information is used for no other purpose than to provide our services to you. Santu does not sell products, offer services, request information or intentionally collect personally identifiable contact information from peope under the age of 18.

### Disclosure and sharing of information

Santu is dedicated to protecting merchants and consumers personally identifiable information.

We only disclose and share such information; when you authorize consent, when a third party, such as banks or credit card processors, require the information in the provision of products and services you have requested, when it is necessary to comply with the law, when a product or service is provided to you by Santu business partners and/or companies who work on behalf of GlobeCharge, when the enforcement of the terms and conditions of our Merchant Agreement is required, when the information may reduce risk and/or protect against fraud in the exchange of information with other organizations.

### Future privacy policy amendments

When you register with Santu, we request your contact information (including your name, residential address and e-mail address), as well as specific information about your business, including bank account and/or credit card numbers.

The information collected by Santu is used to carry out your requests for particular products and services; to facilitate billing; to process payment transactions; and to otherwise provide our services to you. Merchants may also be sent announcements regarding; new Santu products and services, periodic specials, newsletters, service announcements, products and services offered by Santu's business partners.
